Socks Was Sleeping.
Socks was sleeping on the bed. 
Wake up, Socks! I said. 
Socks was sleeping on my chair. 
I said, wake up, Socks! 
She was sleeping on the couch. 
Wake up, Socks! I said. 
She was sleeping on the rug. 
I said, wake up, Socks! 
She was sleeping by the window. 
I said, Socks, wake up! 
Socks was sleeping by the door. 
Wake up! I said. 
Socks was sleeping under the table. 
I can wake Socks up, I said. 
Purr.