A Fast Fox.
Andy Fox saw a rabbit hopping down the road. 
I want to hop like that rabbit, he said. 
Okay. Let's hop! Said mother Fox. 
Andy and mother Fox hopped and hopped. 
I can hop. 
But I can't hop like a rabbit, said Andy. 
No, a fox can't hop like a rabbit, said mother Fox. 
Andy saw a fish in the lake. 
I want to swim like that fish, he said. 
Okay. Let's swim, said his mother. 
Andy and mother fox went for a swim. 
I can swim. 
But I can't swim like a fish, Andy said. 
No, a fox can't swim like a fish, Andy, said mother Fox. 
Andy saw a bird fly by. 
I want to fly! He said. 
Andy, foxes can't fly, said his mother. 
But it was too late. 
Andy flapped his arms. 
He ran and he jumped. 
He fell. 
I can't fly at all, he cried. 
No, Andy. 
Foxes can not fly, said mother Fox. 
I can't do anything! Said Andy. 
Look, Andy. 
I see father and Roxy, said mother Fox. 
Let's go and meet them. 
Let's run as fast as we can. 
Andy and mother Fox ran. 
They met father and Roxy. 
Mother fox said, you ran very fast, Andy! 
You ran as fast as a fox. 
I am a fox! Said Andy. 
Yes, you are, said father Fox. 
And a fox can run very fast. 
Let's run some more, said Andy. 
Let's run as fast as a fox! 
And they did. 