The Muddy Mess.
Dad's car was a muddy mess. 
There was mud on the top. 
There was mud on the tires. 
There was mud everywhere! 
Jake's bike was a muddy mess, too. 
Hey Dad, Jake said. 
I can help you clean your car. 
Then you can help me clean my bike. 
That is a good plan, dad said. 
Dad got two pails. 
He gave one pail to Jake. 
Dad put soap in the pails. 
Then Jake filled the pails. 
Dad and Jake washed the car. 
Dad washed the top. 
Jake washed the tires. 
Look at all this mud, said Jake. 
We need more soap.  
Jake and his dad washed the mud off the car. 
Then they washed the muddy bike. 
My bike is nice and clean, said Jake. 
My car is clean, too, said Dad. 
Let's go eat lunch! 
Oh no! Said Mom. 
Now you two are a muddy mess! 