Mousing the Babysitter.
Moosling liked baby animals, and baby animals loved Moosling. 
He let them climb up his legs. 
He let them ride on his back. 
He let them hang on his antlers. 
He never got mad. 
He never shouted. 
He made sure the little ones did not get hurt. 
Mothers and fathers asked Moosling to babysit all the time. 
One day, skunk asked Moosling to watch the little skunks. 
Moosling said yes. 
He liked the baby skunks. 
They never ran away or climbed too high or fell in the pond. 
They just followed Moosling in a line, like good little skunks. 
You have to be careful, said skunk. 
Don't make them mad, and don't scare them. 
You know why, don't you? 
Moosling did know why. 
Skunks, even little skunks, can make a very, very bad smell when they are upset. 
I will not make them mad, and I would never scare them, said Moosling. 
Then he and the little skunks begin to play. 
Skunk went off down the road. 
But he did not get far. 
Oh no! He said. 
I forgot to tell Moosling one very important thing. 
He ran back. 
Moosling! Moosling! He called. 
I forgot to tell you something! 
Don't sing! Said skunk. 
But it was too late. 
Moosling smelled very bad for a long time. 
But the baby animals didn't mind. 
They loved him too much to stay away. 