The Drip.
Get up. 
Get up, Pop! Said Nana, We have a drip. 
Pop did not get up. 
So Nana got up to fix the drip. 
I will fix the drip, said Nana. 
She put a sock on it. 
The sock did not fix the drip. 
Pop! 
Get up! Said Nana. 
But Pop did not get up. 
I can fix this drip, said Nana. 
She put tape on it. 
The tape did not fix the drip. 
Come on, Pop! 
Get up! Said Nana. 
Pop did not get up. 
I have to fix this drip, said Nana. 
She put a balloon on it. 
Pop got up. 
