Shopping.
Get some milk, said Mom. 
I put the milk in the cart. 
Get some apples, said Mom. 
I put the apples in the cart. 
Get some bananas, Mom said. 
I put the bananas in the cart. 
Mom said, get some oranges. 
I put some oranges in the cart. 
Get some carrots, Mom said. 
I put the carrots in the cart. 
Get some tomatoes, Mom said. 
I put the tomatoes in the cart. 
Get some bread, said Mom. 
I put the bread in the cart. 
Get some cookies, I said. 
Mom put the cookies in the cart. 